<PARTH KETAN DOSHI>

</SOFTWARE ENGINEER>

147/5 Pushpa Park, Garodia Nagar, Ghatkopar (East), Mumbai - 400077
+918169664802 parth.doshi@sakec.ac.in parthdoshi97@gmail.com

parthketandoshi.github.iolinkedin.com/in/parthketandoshi

inikedii.com/in/partiketando

github.com/parthketandoshi

behance.net/parthketandoshi

I am a Computer Engineer with a Passion for Programming, a Knack for Problem Solving, and an Aptitude for Learning, I am curious about various technologies and driven to explore them. I am a quick learner and capable of applying my knowledge concurrently. I have had a plethora of experiences and have made good out of all the opportunities that I have received.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Computer Engineering

Shah & Anchor Kutchhi Engineering College University of Mumbai, Mumbai October 2020 | 6.92 CGPA / 65.16%

Higher Secondary Certificate (Science)

KJ Somaiya College of Science & Commerce Maharashtra State Board, Mumbai February 2015 | 66.46%

Secondary School Certificate

Holy Family High School Maharashtra State Board, Mumbai March 2013 | **87.82%**

PUBLICATION

"Survey on IoT based Bridge Health Monitoring Systems", IJRESM Journal (ISSN (Online) - 2581-5792), Volume-3, Issue-4, April-2020 (Impact Factor: 4.308)

TRAININGS

- Android App Development
- Python 3.x App Development
- iOS App Development
- Spoken Tutorial project by IIT Bombay for C, Java, Python, PHP, MySQL & LaTeX
- Google Assistant at Developer Weekend

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- C, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JS, XML, PHP, SQL, Swift, AppleScript, RegEx
- Angular, Firebase, Cross-platform App Development, Front-end Development, IoT, Dialogflow, Google Collab, Power BI, DBMS, AI/ML
- Terminal, Visual Studio Code, Xcode, Android Studio, API, Cryptography, GFX, Hatch XR, MIT App Inventor, Codepen, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Inkscape, AR/VR, UI/UX, Linux, Raspberry Pi, GitHub, GitLab, BitBucket, Jira, Jenkins, GoCD, Sonarqube
- Cross-functional team leadership, Organisation & Management, Research, Communication Skills, Creative Writing

LANGUAGES KNOWN

English, Gujarati, Hindi, and Marathi

HOBBIES

Trekking, Swimming, Musical Keyboard, and Exploring new Technologies

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Zycus Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

Associate Software Engineer (April 2021 - Present)

- Worked on enhancements, feature development, bug fixes as well as CI/CD
- Implemented Java version upgrade and its adoption for one of the products
- Icon creation and externalization based on product requirements
- Core member of Funzastic committee organizing cultural and fun activities

Trainee Software Engineer (January 2021 - April 2021)

- Underwent extensive training on Angular and implemented a project
- Joined the CoE team working on different products and technologies
- Implemented fixes for issues raised in SonarQube Reports
- Created a dashboard to present data for consumption by different teams

Camp K12 - Tech Mentor (April 2020 - May 2020)

 Taught Android App Development on MIT App Inventor, 3D coding, and VR using HatchXR and HTML, CSS & JS using CodePen to school students

Fube Technology - Software Development Intern (January 2019 - April 2020)

 Worked on Yodais and Jom Channel products for Fube Technology, Malaysia for the Front-end development of a Bootstrap based website

Trivia Software - Android & Python App Dev Intern (June 2018 - July 2018)

- Developed an Android App for Calculating BMI in which we implemented UI,
 APIs, shared preferences, and a unique interactive splash screen
- Implemented a desktop app using python to manage a student database and incorporated GUI, APIs, and different Packages in this project

Toppr - WordPress Admin & SEO Manager Intern (February 2018 - June 2018)

 Joined as a content writer and editor and further worked on WordPress Administration, MathJAX, SEO and also managing other writers

PROJECTS

Real-Time Bridge Monitoring System Capstone Project (July 2019 - April 2020)

Developed a comprehensive IoT project for Bridge Health Monitoring which comprises Sensors for checking vibrations and bending on structure, Python-based Applications for Image & Audio Processing, and a PWA for output

Angular Assessment Project (February 2020)

Developed an Angular web application fetching data from JSONPlaceholder APIs, cross-referencing it and displaying it appropriately

Production Application Test (March 2020)

Implemented solution for Intercom hiring problem statement in Python using Jupyter Notebook along with unit-testing and hosted it with firebase

Gujarati & Marathi News Headlines Classification (May 2020)

Implemented Text Classification for Gujarati and Marathi Languages in Google Collab using NLP and datasets from Kaggle based on iNLTK Python Library

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCES

- Volunteer at Teach For India for project under Teach to Lead Foundation
- General Secretary of ISTE SAKEC Students' Chapter for A.Y. 2017-18
- Organising Head for Industrial Visit and Outbound Activity
- Core Team Member of TAPtheTECH (NGO & Coursera Learning Hub)

ACHIEVEMENTS

- · Zycus individual recognition for commendable performance & agility
- Guest Speaker for Tech Routes webinar organised by CSI-KJSCE
- Cracked Google HashCode, TCS CodeVita, and Infosys HackWithInfy
- INSPIRE Award by Department of Science & Technology